Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 8 and District 8 Locals, 1936-1957 UE.4.1.8
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 8 Locals, 2.
  - Local 813
    - Local 813 Faultless Caster Negotiations, November 23, 1945 - April 24, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 68)
      - Albert Fitzgerald to William Sentner, November 23, 1945; 1.
      - Sentner to Fitzgerald, March 22, 1946; 2.
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement, Apirl 24, 1946; 3.
    - Local 813 Evansville CIO, April 21 - 22, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 69)
      - Charles Wright to Phillip Murray Regarding Evansville CIO Resolution, April 21, 1947; 1.
      - Wright to John Brophy, April 22, 1947; 2.
    - Local 813 Bucyrus Erie Inter-union Rivalry, January 13 - May 9, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 70)
      - William Sentner to Julius Emspak, January 13, 1947; 1.
      - William Fauer to Emspak, January 13, 1947; 2.
      - Emspak to Fauer, January 20, 1947; 3.
      - Otto Maschoff to James Matles, May 9, 1947; 4.
    - Local 813 Subsidy, February 19 - March 4, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 71)
      - William Sentner to Julius Emspak, February 19, 1947; 1.
      - James Matles to Sentner, March 4, 1947; 2.
    - Local 813 Bucyrus Erie Strike, May 3 - August 31, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 72)
      - N.R. Knox to William Senter with May 4, 1948, James Payne Letter to Albert Fitzgerald, May 3, 1948; 1.
      - Bert Miller to Robert Fischer, August 31, 1948; 2.
    - Local 813 Seeger Strike, April 29 - 30, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 73)
      - Union Proposals, April 29, 1948; 1.
      - Termination of Strike Notice, April 30, 1948; 2.
    - Local 813 Financial Situation, December 1948 (Box 4, Folder 74)
      - Strike Fund Data, December 1948; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Joseph Pogue, December 27, 1938; 2.
    - Local 813 Seeger Factionalism and United Auto Workers Rivalry, May 5 - June 17, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 75)
      - William Sentner to James Matles, May 5, 1949; 1.
      - Otto Maschoff to Albert Fitzgerald, June 17, 1949; 2.
    - Local 813 King Resignation, August 24 - 26, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 76)
      - Julius Emspak to Joseph Pogue with August 22, 1949, Alvis King Letter to Emspak, August 24, 1949; 1.
      - Joseph Pogue to Emspak, August 26, 1949; 2.
    - Local 813 Charters, August 15 - October 6, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 77)
      - Local 813 Executive Board Statement, August 15, 1949; 1.
      - Joseph Pogue to Julius Emspak, August 26, 1949; 2.
      - Emspak to Pogue, August 31, 1949; 3.
      - William Sentner to James Matles, September 2, 1949; 4.
      - Emspak to Pogue, October 6, 1949; 5.
    - Local 813 Seeger Stirke and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, November 13 - December 24, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 78)
      - Robert Logsdon to James Matles with Newspaper Clippings, November 13, 1951; 1.
      - James Payne to All Servel Members, December 4, 1951; 2.
      - William Sentner to James Matles, December 4, 1951; 3.
      - Sentner to Matles, December 12, 1951; 4.
      - Logsdon to Matles, December 13, 1951; 5.
      - Sentner to Matles, December 13, 1951; 6.
      - Logsdon to Matles, December 1951; 7.
      - Statement, December 18, 1951; 8.
      - Logsdon to Matles, December 24, 1951; 9.
    - Local 813 Servel Negotiations, June 21 - 29, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 79)
      - Robert Logsdon to Albert Fitzgerald, June 21, 1954; 1.
      - Letter to Logsdon, June 21, 1954; 2.
      - Elmer Ralph Memo, June 29, 1954; 3.
    - Local 813 Staff and Finances, March 8, 1954 - June 30, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 80)
      - Emma Memo to Dave Ratner, March 8, 1954; 1.
      - James Matles Memo to Janet, April 7, 1954; 2.
      - Robert Logsdon to Matles, April 22, 1954; 3.
      - Don Harris to Matles, April 29, 1954; 4.
      - Logsdon to Matles, June 30, 1955; 5.
    - Local 813 Correspondence, September 29, 1942 - August 14, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 81)
      - William Sentner to Julius Emspak Regarding Disbanding, September 29, 1942; 1.
      - Sunbeam Resolution Regarding Negotiations, October 18, 1942; 2.
      - James Payne to James Matles Regarding Officers and Staff Members, December 16, 1942; 3.
      - Memo Regarding Address Change, April 1945; 4.
      - Shop Delegates Conference Proceedings, July 21, 1946; 5.
      - UE Committee for Democratic Action Statement Regarding Officers, August 14, 1946; 6.
    - Local 813 Correspondence, December 12, 1946 - October 1948 (Box 4, Folder 82)
      - Memo Regarding Wages, December 12, 1946; 1.
      - Memo Regarding Activity Report, January 8, 1947; 2.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to William Sentner Regaridng Evansville Visit, June 4, 1947; 3.
      - Fitzgerald to Sentner Regarding Bucyrus Erie Strikes, July 30, 1947; 4.
      - John Krueger to Fitzgerald Regarding Seeger Strike, December 15, 1947; 5.
      - Union Negotiation Proposals Regarding Servel, March 4, 1948; 6.
      - Bucyrus Erie Conference Memo, March 6, 1948; 7.
      - Grievance Report Regarding Servel, April 13, 1948; 8.
      - Organizational Program, June 17, 1948; 9.
      - Sentner to Joseph Dermondy Regarding Seeger Contract, June 18, 1948; 10.
      - Election Totals Regarding Factionalism and Officers, August 1948; 11.
      - Memo Regarding Factionalism, October 1948; 12.
    - Local 813 Correspondence, March 22, 1949 - June 17, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 83)
      - Report of Negotiating Committee Regarding Servel with March 7, 1949, Contract Report, March 22, 1949; 1.
      - Resolution on Unemployment, March 29, 1949; 2.
      - Grievance Report with William Sentner Letter to Albert Fitzgerald, May 23, 1949; 3.
      - Agreement Regarding Separate Seeger Charter, August 31, 1949; 4.
      - IUE Local 808 Officers to Members Regarding Strike, August 1950; 5.
      - Proposed Contract Settlement Regarding Servel with Sadelle Berger Memo to Albert Fitzgerald, 1951; 6.
      - Berger to James Matles Regarding Finances, August 15, 1951; 7.
      - Robert Logsdon to Matles Regarding Servel Negotiations, Seeger and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, June 17, 1951; 8.
    - Local 813 Correspondnece, June 1956 (Box 4, Folder 84)
      - Servel Check-off Revocation, June 1956; 1.
      - National Labor Relations Board and American Federation of Labor, Undated; 2.
      - Contract Proposal Resolution Regarding Seeger, Undated; 3.
      - Auto Workers Rank and File Minutes, Undated; 4.
  - Local 814
    - Local 814 Officers Lists, October 1, 1942 - August 12, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 85)
    - Local 814 Officer Meeting Minutes, July 14 - August 12, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 86)
    - Local 814 Membership Meeting Minutes, August 17, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 87)
    - Local 814 Membership Resolution Regarding World War II, the British and Soviet Union, May 1942 (Box 4, Folder 88)
    - Local 814 Incoming Correspondence, August 29, 1944 - August 13, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 89)
      - Julius Emspak to Daisy Smith Regarding Finances, August 29, 1944; 1.
      - Emspak to Ivan Wolf Regarding War Labor Board, June 15, 1945; 2.
      - Emspak to Thorsten Franzeen Regarding Dues and Veterans, June 18, 1945; 3.
      - Emspak to Wolf Regaridng Herman Nelson Strike, February 18, 1946; 4.
      - Emspak to Franzeen Regarding Per Capita, December 23, 1946; 5.
      - Emspak to Lee Thompson Regarding Wages, June 6, 1947; 6.
      - Emspak to Thompson Regarding Political Action Committee, November 18, 1947; 7.
      - Emspak to Thompson Regarding Political Action Committee, December 2, 1947; 8.
      - Emspak to Thompson Regarding Finances, March 30, 1948; 9.
      - Emspak to Rex Wheelock Regarding Eagle Signal Strike and Wages, Apirl 27, 1948; 10.
      - Emspak to Wheelock Regarding Eagle Signal and Herman Nelson Strikes, May 28, 1948; 11.
      - Emspak to Thompson Regarding Eagle Signal and Herman Nelson Strikes, May 28, 1948; 12.
      - Emspak to Wheelock Regarding Herman Nelson Strike, June 7, 1948; 13.
      - Emspak to Roy Saltz Regarding Minneapolis Moline Charter, July 30, 1948; 14.
      - Emspak to Thompson Regarding Separate Charters and UE Convention, August 13, 1948; 15.
      - James Matles to J.B. Johnson Regarding Staff Members, November 7, 1946; 16.
      - William Sentner to Dwight Brenston Regarding Factionalism and Separate Charters, November 17, 1944; 17.
      - Sentner to Wheelock Regarding Voss Brothers Organization, June 18, 1945; 18.
      - Sentner to Saltz Regarding Factionalism and Separate Charters, July 27, 1948; 19.
    - Local 814 Outgoing Correspondence, April 6, 1942 - August 20, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 90)
      - G.R. Bloomberg to UE Regarding Officers, April 6, 1942; 1.
      - Kathryn Couchman to Julius Emspak Regarding Per Capita, February 20, 1945; 2.
      - Adrian Curtis to Local 814 Members Regarding Eagle Signal Strike, 1948; 3.
      - E.J. Floyd to Emspak Regarding Eagle Signal Strike, February 5, 1942; 4.
      - Floyd to James Matles Regarding Officers and Iowa Ordinance Organization, March 31, 1942; 5.
      - Thorsten Franzeen to Emspak Regarding Dues and Veterans, June 15, 1945; 6.
      - Franzeen to Emspak Regarding Stirke Fund, January 19, 1946; 7.
      - Franzeen to William Sentner Regarding Strike Fund, April 26, 1946; 8.
      - Franzeen to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, October 5, 1946; 9.
      - Franzeen to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, December 16, 1946; 10.
      - Franzeen Regarding Herman Nelson Strike, Undated; 11.
      - Roy Saltz to Emspak Regarding Factionalism and Minneapolis Moline Separate Charter, July 23, 1948; 12.
      - Lee Thompson to Emspak Regarding Factionalism, UE Convention and Minneapolis Moline Separate Charter, July 31, 1948; 13.
      - Thompson to Emspak Regarding UE Convention, Separate Charters and Minneapolis Moline, August 10, 1948; 14.
      - Thompson to Emspak Regarding Factionalism and UE Convention with August 17, 1948, Emspak Letter to Sentner, August 14, 1948; 15.
      - Thompson to Emspak Regarding Minneapolis Moline Separate Charters, August 18, 1948; 16.
      - Thompson to Emspak Regarding Factionalism and UE Convention, August 20, 1948; 17.
    - Local 814 Outgoing Correspondence, February 28, 1945 - February 1, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 91)
      - Rex Wheelock to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, December 21, 1943; 1.
      - Wheelock to Emspak Regarding Finances, February 28, 1945; 2.
      - Wheelock to Robert Logsdon Regarding Finances, September 4, 1945; 3.
      - Wheelock to Emspak Regarding Staff Finances and Factionalism, November 5, 1948; 4.
      - Wheelock to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, January 2, 1947; 5.
      - Wheelock to Tom Wright Regarding Publicity, December 16, 1947; 6.
      - Wheelock to Emspak Regarding Political Action Committee, December 23, 1947; 7.
      - Wheelock to Emspak Regarding Eagle Signal and Herman Nelson Negotiations, April 19, 1948; 8.
      - Wheelock to Emspak Regarding Eagle Signal and Herman Nelson Strikes, May 17, 1948; 9.
      - Wheelock to Emspak Regarding Herman Nelson and Eagle Signal Contracts, June 4, 1948; 10.
      - Ivan Wolf to Emspak Regarding Herman Nelson War Labor Board, June 12, 1945; 11.
      - Wolf to James Matles Regarding UE Officers, Factionalism and Political Action Committee, November 2, 1945; 12.
      - Wolf to Matles Regaridng Herman Nelson Strike, February 1, 1946; 13.
      - Strike Strategy Committee to Catterton Regarding Herman Nelson Strike, Undated; 14.
    - Locla 814 Finances, Bonding Form and Trustees Statement, February 17, 1942, August 21, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 92)
    - Local 814 Leaflets, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 93)
      - "No Work After 10A.M." Regarding Herman Nelson Strike, 1948; 1.
      - "A Challenge" Regarding Herman Nelson Strike, undated; 2.
    - Local 814 Newspaper 814 Bulletin, undated (Box 4, Folder 94)
    - Local 814 Eagle Signal Organization, January 1942 (Box 4, Folder 95)
      - Owen Smith to James Matles, January 24, 1942; 1.
      - Charter Application, January 24, 1942; 2.
      - Brief History, January 1942; 3.
      - Julius Emspak to Smith, January 26, 1942; 4.
      - Stella to William Sentner, January 26, 1942; 5.
      - Emspak to Smith, January 28, 1942; 6.
      - Emspak to Smith, January 30, 1942; 7.
    - Local 814 Amalgamation, July - November 4, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 96)
      - Resolution of Locals 814 and 815, July 1942; 1.
      - Minutes, September 15, 1942; 2.
      - John Nordman to Julius Emspak, October 1942; 3.
      - Joint Executive Board Resolution, October 1, 1942; 4.
      - Emspak to Nordman, November 4, 1942; 5.
      - Joint Executive Board Resolution, 1942; 6.
    - Local 814 Eagle Signal Wages, January 6 - April 20, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 97)
      - M. Porosky to Rex Wheelock, January 6, 1944; 1.
      - Wheelock to Porosky, January 12, 1944; 2.
      - Wheelock to Porosky, April 20, 1944; 3.
    - Local 814 Minneapolis Moline Separate Charters, November 28 - December 4, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 98)
      - Ray Klausner to William Sentner, November 28, 1944; 1.
      - Sentner to Julius Emspak, December 4, 1944; 2.
    - Local 814 Herman Nelson Strike, February 11 - May 21, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 99)
      - William Sentner to Julius Emspak, February 11, 1946; 1.
      - Rex Wheelock to Emspak, February 20, 1946; 2.
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement, April 15, 1946; 3.
      - Wheelock to Sentner, April 18, 1946; 4.
      - Wheelock to Emspak, April 18, 1946; 5.
      - Wheelock to Emspak, April 19, 1946; 6.
      - Wheelock to Emspak, April 22, 1946; 7.
      - Edward Pringle to Wheelock, May 1946; 8.
      - Wheelock to Emspak, May 18, 1946; 9-10.
      - Emspak to Wheelock, May 21, 1946; 11.
      - Wheelock to Robert Logsdon, May 21, 1946; 12.
      - Wheelock to Emspak, May 21, 1946; 13.
      - Wage Petition, 1940; 14.
    - Local 814 Local Division, July 16 - August 23, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 100)
      - Special Committee Minutes, July 16, 1948; 1.
      - Stipulation of Agreement, July 16, 1948; 2.
      - Amendment to Stipulation, August 2, 1948; 3.
      - William Sentner to Julius Emspak, August 10, 1948; 4.
      - Convention Credentials, August 14, 1948; 5.
      - Vote Totals, August 18, 1948; 6.
      - Lee Thompson Statement, August 20, 1948; 7.
      - Sentner to Emspak, August 23, 1948; 8.
      - Committee Minutes, August 23, 1948; 9.
    - Local 814 Correspondence, January 30, 1941 - December 1, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 101)
      - Otto Maschoff to Julius Emspak Regarding Charter, January 30, 1941; 1.
      - Vote Total Regarding Herman Nelson Organization and Inter-union Rivalry with International Association of Machinists, April 14, 1943; 2.
      - Porosky to H.G. Lewis Regarding Eagle Signal Wages and War Labor Board, December 23, 1943; 3.
      - Rex Wheelock to Emspak Regarding Factionalism and Stewards, February 6, 1944; 4.
      - David Scribner to Alice Smith Regarding War Labor Board, June 15, 1945; 5.
      - Wheelock to Ernest DeMaio Regarding Minneapolis Moline Negotiations, February 20, 1946; 6.
      - Executive Board Statement Regaridng UE Officers and Wages, June 2, 1947; 7.
      - Termination of Herman Nelson Strike, June 14, 1948; 8.
      - Scribner to Robert Logsdon Regarding Finances, December 1, 1949; 9.
      - Picket Card Regarding Herman Nelson, Undated; 10.
  - Local 815 (Moline)
    - Local 815 (Moline) Outgoing Correspondence, April 12 - June 23, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 102)
      - Alfred Bracewell to Julius Emspak Regarding Supplies, April 12, 1942; 1.
      - Tom Willits to Emspak Regarding Finances, June 23, 1942; 2.
    - Local 815 (Moline) Bonding Questionnaire and Form, June 23 - July 1, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 103)
    - Local 815 (Moline) Leaflets, June 1942 (Box 4, Folder 104)
      - "Lets Go CIO" Regarding Reynolds Organization, June 24, 1942; 1.
      - "Who Is Patriotric" Regarding Reynolds Organization, June 1942; 2.
      - "Tool Workers Get the Bait" Regarding Minneapolis Moline Organization, June 1942; 3.
      - "The UE-CIO Record" Regarding Organization, June 1942; 4.
    - Local 815 (Moline) Organization, April 1942 (Box 4, Folder 105)
      - Owen Smith to Julius Emspak, April 1942; 1.
      - Emspak to Smith, April 12, 1942; 2.
      - Charter Application, April 1942; 3.
    - Local 815 (Moline) War Orders, May 13 - June 13, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 106)
      - Owen Smith to Russ Nixon, May 13, 1942; 1.
      - Nixon to Smith, May 19, 1942; 2.
      - Production Survey, May 19, 1942; 3.
      - Nixon to W.R. Tracy, May 19, 1942; 4.
      - Smith to Julius Emspak, May 20, 1942; 5.
      - Smith to Nixon, May 25, 1942; 6.
      - Nixon to Smith, June 13, 1942; 7.
    - Local 815 (Moline) Correspondence, Julius Emspak to John Dordiman Regarding Amalgamation, October 12, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Local 815 (Memphis)
    - Local 815 (Memphis) Officers Lists, February 1948 (Box 4, Folder 108)
    - Local 815 (Memphis) Correspondence, Julius Emspak to E. Mullin Regarding Organization, February 10, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 109)
    - Local 815 (Memphis) Stamps, February 17 - March 18, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 110)
    - Local 815 (Memphis) Charter Supplies, February 10, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 111)
    - Local 815 (Memphis) Organization, February 10 - April 30, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 112)
      - Julius Emspak to Otto Maschoff, February 10, 1948; 1.
      - Emspak to William Sentner, February 10, 1948; 2.
      - Maschoff to Emspak, April 30, 1948; 3.
  - Local 815 (Keosauqua)
    - Local 815 (Keosauqua) Finances, August 26 - September 1, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 113)
      - Stamps, August 26, 1952; 1.
      - Ledger, August 1952; 2.
      - Charter Supplies, September 1, 1952; 3.
    - Local 815 (Keosauqua) Newspaper Clippings, September 10, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 114)
      - "Berker at Keosauqua Officers Wage Boosts", Undated; 1.
      - "Strike Stops Contract Meeting at Keosauqua", September 10, 1952; 2.
    - Local 815 (Keosauqua) Organization and Strike, August 2 - October 7, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 115)
      - Don Harris to Julius Emspak, August 2, 1952; 1.
      - Emspak to Charles Hobbie, August 27, 1952; 2.
      - Emspak to Harris, August 27, 1952; 3.
      - Emspak to George Eddy, August 27, 1952; 4.
      - Charter Application, September 1, 1952; 5.
      - Injunction Notice, September 19, 1952; 6.
      - Injunction, September 29, 1952; 7.
      - Basil Pollitt Memo, October 7, 1952; 8.
  - Local 816 (St. Louis)
    - Local 816 (St. Louis) Officers Lists, September 12, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 116)
    - Local 816 (St. Louis) Incoming Correspondence, July 22 - December 18, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 117)
      - Julius Emspak to Gary LaDassor Regarding Bonding, July 22, 1942; 1.
      - Emspak to LaDassor Regarding Bonding, April 22, 1942; 2.
      - Emspak to Harry Smith Regarding Bonding, Novebmer 9, 1942; 3.
      - James Matles to Smith Regarding Staff Members, December 18, 1942; 4.
    - Local 816 (St. Louis) Outgoing Correspondence, April 15, 1943 - January 23, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 118)
      - Gary LaDassor to Julius Emspak Regarding Dues and Bonding, April 15, 1943; 1.
      - LaDassor to Emspak Regarding Per Capita and Negotiations, August 11, 1943; 2.
      - A.F. Reineck to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, January 23, 1946; 3.
    - Local 816 (St. Louis) Bonding Questionnaire and Form, November 23 - December 9, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 119)
    - Local 816 (St. Louis) Financial Reports, February 1943 (Box 4, Folder 120)
    - Local 816 (St. Louis) US Cartridge Election Notice, May 1943 (Box 4, Folder 121)
    - Local 816 (St. Louis) US Cartridge Organization, July 17 - December 1, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 122)
      - Charter Application, July 17, 1942; 1.
      - William Sentner to Julius Emspak, July 24, 1942; 2.
      - Emspak to Sentner, July 20, 1942; 3.
      - Neil Brant to Sentner, August 18, 1942; 4.
      - Emspak to Sentner, October 6, 1942; 5.
      - Sentner to Emspak, October 12, 1942; 6.
      - Frances Sayler to Sentner, November 17, 1942; 7.
      - Emspak to Sentner, November 17, 1942; 8.
      - Organization Activities Memo Regarding US Cartridge, November 18, 1942; 9.
      - Sentner to Russ Nixon, November 19, 1942; 10.
      - Nixon to James Matles with Nixon Letter to Sentner, November 20, 1942; 11.
      - Brant to Matles, December 1, 1942; 12.
    - Local 816 (St. Louis) Correspondence, May 10, 1943 - July 8, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 123)
      - Williaim Sentner to James Matles Regarding US Cartridge Wages, May 10, 1943; 1.
      - Sentner to Julius Emspak Regarding Disbanding, July 8, 1946; 2.
  - Local 816 (Fulton)
    - Local 816 (Fulton) Correspondence, Julius Emspak to Laurence Knapp, September 3, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 124)
    - Local 816 (Fulton) Charter Supplies and Financial Ledger, September 3, 1952 - April 1953 (Box 4, Folder 125)
    - Local 816 (Fulton) Organization, August 29 - September 3, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 126)
      - Don Harris to Julius Emspak, August 29, 1952; 1.
      - Emspak to Harris, September 3, 1952; 2.
  - Local 817 (Cairo)
    - Local 817 (Cairo) Incoming Correspondence, September 24 - October 14, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 127)
      - Julius Emspak to Byron Alcorn, September 24, 1942; 1.
      - Lou Kimmel to War Workers, October 14, 1942; 2.
    - Local 817 (Cairo) Bonding Form, September 24, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 128)
    - Local 817 (Cairo) Organization, September 24 - December 30, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 129)
      - Julius Emspak to Lou Kimmel, September 24, 1942; 1.
      - Russ Nixon to James Matles with Nixon Letter to William Sentner, September 29, 1942; 2.
      - Kimmel to Emspak, October 1942; 3.
      - Sentner to Nixon, October 27, 1942; 4.
      - Sentner to Emspak with Bills, November 17, 1942; 5.
      - Emspak to Sentner, November 27, 1942; 6.
      - Sentner to Emspak, December 30, 1942; 7.
  - Local 817 (Lawrence)
    - Local 817 (Lawrence) Officers Lists, June 24, 1948 - March 7, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 130)
    - Local 817 (Lawrence) Incoming Correspondence, March 15, 1948 - February 26, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 131)
      - Julius Emspak to Lester Anderson Regarding Organization, March 15, 1948; 1.
      - Emspak to Lucille Bond Regarding Supplies and Per Capita, March 10, 1950; 2.
      - Emspak to Bond Regarding Disbanding, February 26, 1951; 3.
    - Local 817 (Lawrence) Outgoing Correspondence, Lucille Bond to UE Regarding Disbanding, February 20, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 132)
    - Local 817 (Lawrence) Charter Supplies, March 8, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 133)
    - Local 817 (Lawrence) Organization, March 15, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 134)
      - Julius Emspak to William Sentner, March 15, 1948; 1.
      - Emspak to Robert Logsdon, March 15, 1948; 2.
      - Charter Information, 1948; 3.
    - Local 817 (Lawrence) Charter Reinstatement, February 3 - March 10, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 135)
      - Robert Logsdon to James Matles, February 3, 1950; 1.
      - Emma Memo to Rachie, February 7, 1950; 2.
      - Otto Maschoff to Julius Emspak, March 7, 1950; 3.
      - Emspak to Maschoff, March 10, 1950; 4.
    - Local 817 (Lawrence) Correspondence, February 26, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 136)
      - Secretary of Julius Emspak to William Sentner Regarding Disbanding, February 26, 1951; 1.
      - M.A. Myers Regarding Organization, Undated; 2.
  - Local 818
    - Local 818 Officers Lists, July 1943 - March 18, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 137)
    - Local 818 Membership List with September 17, 1949, Bernell Tolbert Letter to Julius Emspak, July 24, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 138)
    - Local 818 Incoming Correspondence, September 24, 1942 - March 14, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 139)
      - Julius Emspak to Joseph Daily Regarding Bonding, September 24, 1942; 1.
      - Emspak to Fred Colbert Regarding Political Action, December 15, 1943; 2.
      - Emspak to Laverne Gregory Regarding Dues and Veterans, January 15, 1945; 3.
      - Emspak to Albert Combs Regarding Dues and Veterans, February 23, 1945; 4.
      - Emspak to Combs Regarding Per Capita, May 3, 1945; 5.
      - Emspak to Colbert, July 30, 1945; 6.